Register of the Ernest Lundeen Papers, 1860-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1906-1942
  - Hoidale, Einar (Folder 7)
  - Holmberg, N. J. (Folder 8)
  - Holmes, Emil E. (Folder 9)
  - Hoover, Herbert (Folder 10)
  - Housing
    - General (Box 260., Folder 1-2)
    - Federal Housing Authority (Folder 3)
  - Humpfner, Hilda (Folder 4)
  - Hungary (Folder 5)
  - Iceland (Folder 6)
  - Immigration (Folder 7)
  - Import-Export Bank (Folder 8)
  - Imports
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Manganese (Folder 10)
  - Income, Distribution of
    - Farm (Folder 11)
    - Fortunes (Folder 12)
    - U.S. (Box 261., Folder 1)
  - India (Folder 2)
  - Indians, American (Folder 3)
  - Industrial and capital mobilization (Folder 4)
  - Industrial Expansion Act (Folder 5)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (Folder 6)
  - Industry (Folder 7)
  - Injunction cases (1920) (Folder 8)
  - Insurance (1912-) (Folder 9)
  - International Grain Company (Folder 10)
  - International Joint Commission (previously, the International Waterways Commission) (Folder 11)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Folder 12)
  - Investors (Folder 13)
  - Ireland (Folder 14)
  - Iron ore (Folder 15)
  - Irrigation (Folder 16)
  - Islands
    - General (Folder 17)
    - Acquisitions of islands within 1500 miles of Panama (Folder 18)
      - Canton and Enderbury (Folder 19)
      - Caribbean (Box 262., Folder 1)
      - Legislation
        - Lundeen, Ernest (Folder 2)
        - Reynolds, Robert (Folder 3)
      - Monroe Doctrine (Folder 4)
      - St. Pierre and Miquelon (Folder 5)
      - Virgin Islands (Folder 6)
      - Warship exchange (Folder 7)
      - West Indies (Folder 8)
  - Isolationism (Folder 9)
  - Italy
    - General (Folder 10)
    - War debts (Folder 11)
  - Japan
    - General (Folder 12)
    - General (Box 263., Folder 1)
    - Embargo (Folder 2)
    - 1911 Treaty termination (Folder 3)
  - Jefferson, Thomas (Folder 4)
  - Jerdee, Mons E. (Folder 5)
  - Jews
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Andrew (Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Hiram (Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Magnus
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Lundeen speech at dedication of memorial monument (Folder 11)
  - Justices, U.S. Supreme Court (Box 264., Folder 1)
  - Keller, Helen (Folder 2)
  - Kelly, Eugene (Folder 3)
  - Knights of Columbus (Folder 4)
  - Ku Klux Klan (Folder 5)
  - La Follette, Philip (Folder 6)
  - La Follette, Robert M. (Folder 7)
  - La Guardia, Fiorello (Folder 8)
  - Labor
    - General
      - Miscellany (Folder 9-10)
      - Clippings (Box 265., Folder 1-2)
    - American Federation of Labor
      - General (Folder 3)
      - AFL-CIO controversy (Folder 4)
    - American Labor Party (Folder 5)
    - Conference for Progressive Labor Action (Folder 6)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (Folder 7)
    - Corporations (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Folder 9)
    - Great Britain
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Labor Party (Folder 11)
    - Leaders
      - Green, William (Folder 12)
      - Hillman, Sidney (Folder 13)
      - Hillstrom, Joseph (Joe Hill) (Box 266., Folder 1)
      - Lasser, David (Folder 2)
      - Lewis, John L. (Folder 3)
    - Legislation
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Minnesota
        - Lundeen bill, House File 34, 1911 (Folder 5)
        - Lundeen bill, House File 787, 1911 (Folder 6)
    - Maritime Union (Folder 7)
    - Minnesota (Folder 8)
      - Building Trades Council (Folder 9)
    - Problems (Folder 10)
    - Strikes (Folder 11)
    - Wages (Folder 12)
      - Wages and Hours bill (Box 267., Folder 1)
      - Wages and Hours law (Folder 2)
      - Wagner Act (Folder 3)
      - Wagner Labor Disputes bill (Folder 4)
      - Wagner-Lewis Unemployment Insurance bill (Folder 5)
  - Labor Day, 1912 (Folder 6)
  - Labor Party - Hawaii (Folder 7)
  - Lansing, Robert (Folder 8)
  - Latvia (Folder 9)
  - League for Independent Political Action (Folder 10)
  - League of Nations (Folder 11)
  - League of Women Voters (Folder 12)
  - Lecture notes and ideas (Folder 13)
  - Legislators, U.S.
    - Alabama - Michigan (Box 268., Folder 1)
    - Minnesota (Folder 2)
    - Mississippi - New Jersey (Folder 3)
    - New Mexico - Oregon (Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania - Wyoming (Folder 5)
  - Lewis, James Hamilton (Folder 6)
  - Liberator, April 1920 issue (Box 269., Folder 1)
  - Lien law (Folder 2)
  - Lincoln, Abraham (Folder 3)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A., Jr. (Folder 4)
  - Liquor (Folder 5)
  - Lithuania (Folder 6)
  - Lotteries (Folder 7)
  - Louisiana (Folder 8)
  - Lusitania (Folder 9)
  - MacLeish, Archibald (Folder 10)
  - McLemore Resolution (Folder 11)
  - Markham, Edwin (Folder 12)
  - Maverick, Maury (Folder 13)
  - Mayo, William J. (Folder 14)
  - Medicine, Socialized (Folder 15)
  - Meints case, 1919 (Folder 16)
  - Mencken, Henry L. (Folder 17)
  - Memorial Day, 1919, 1920 (Folder 18)
  - Mexico (Folder 19)
  - Military training in schools (Folder 20)
  - Minneapolis contacts (Folder 21)
  - Minneapolis Journal (Folder 22)
  - Minneapolis Labor Review, 1931 March 27, May 15, July 10 (Folder 23)
  - Minnesota (Folder 24)
  - Minnesota politics (Box 270., Folder 1)
  - Minnesota Swedish population (Folder 2)
  - Minnesota, State of
    - Department of Conservation (Folder 3)
    - Election laws (Folder 4)
    - Public Relations Bureau (Folder 5)
  - Minnesota Daily Star, 1920-1923 (Folder 6)
  - Minnesota Stats Tidning, 1915-1916 (Folder 7)
  - Minnesotans in Washington, D.C. (lists of names) (Folder 8)
  - Minorities (Folder 9)
  - Mississippi River (Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, William (Folder 11)
  - Money (Folder 12-13)
  - Money and political panaceas (Box 271., Folder 1)
  - Monopoly inquiry, 1937-1939 (Folder 2)
  - Monroe Doctrine (Folder 3)
  - Mooney, Tom (Folder 4)
  - Moral Re-armament (Folder 5)
  - Mother's Day (Folder 6)
  - Munitions (Folder 7)
  - Mystic Lodge (Folder 8)
  - National defense
    - General (Folder 9)
    - General (includes lists of military reservations within 300 miles of the Canadian border under control of War Department, and training camps, etc. under control of various states) (Box 272., Folder 1-2)
    - Air defense
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Airplane vs. battleship (Folder 4)
      - Lundeen's Department of Air Service bill (Folder 5)
      - Mitchell, William (Folder 6)
      - Sales to foreign governments (Folder 7)
    - America first (Folder 8)
    - Appropriations (Folder 9)
    - Armaments
      - To 1936 (Folder 10)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 11)
      - Garand and Johnson rifles (Folder 12)
    - Benefactor, vol. 2, no. 14, 15 (1940) (Folder 13)
    - Business (Folder 14)
    - Disarmament (Folder 15)
    - Industry (Folder 16)
    - Merchant Marine (Folder 17)
    - Military strength (Folder 18)
    - National Defense Council (Folder 19)
    - National Guard
      - To 1936 (Box 273., Folder 1)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 2)
    - Pacifists (Folder 3)
    - R.O.T.C. (Folder 4)
    - Resources (Folder 5)
    - Rickenbacker, Eddie (Folder 6)
    - Taxes (Folder 7)
    - United States Army
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Strength (Folder 9)
    - United States Navy
      - General (Folder 10-11)
      - Appropriations
        - General (Folder 12)
        - Lundeen's position (Box 274., Folder 1)
      - President Roosevelt's statements (Folder 2)
      - Secretary of State Hull's statements (Folder 3)
      - Speech draft, n.d. (Folder 4)
      - Submarines
        - To 1936 (Folder 5)
        - 1936-1940 (Folder 6)
  - National Emergency Food Garden Commission, 1917 (Folder 7)
  - National Labor Relations Board (Folder 8)
  - National Live Stock Association (Folder 9)
  - National Park Service (Folder 10)
  - National Party (Folder 11)
  - The Nation's Honor Roll for 1937 (Folder 12)
  - Naval Conference, London, 1930 (Folder 13)
  - Nearing, Scott (Folder 14)
  - Nelson, Martin (Folder 15)
  - Netherlands (Folder 16)
  - New Jersey Canal (Folder 17)
  - Newton, Walter H. (Folder 18)
  - Nicaragua (Folder 19)
  - Northwest Airlines (Folder 20)
  - Norton, W. E. (Folder 21)
  - Norway (Folder 22)
  - Norwegian-American Historical Society (Folder 23)
  - Old age pensions, 1916-1931 (Folder 24)
  - Olson, Floyd B.
    - General (Folder 25)
    - Biography (Box 275., Folder 1)
    - Death; memorials (Folder 2)
    - Speech notes and drafts (Folder 3)
  - Organizations, political
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Societies (Folder 5)
  - Panama (Folder 6)
  - Party platforms, 1923-1929 (Folder 7)
  - Peace
    - General (Box 276., Folder 1)
    - Organizations (Folder 2)
    - Speech material (Folder 3)
  - Persons (Folder 4)
  - Peterson, Hjalmar (Folder 5)
  - Peterson, James A. (Folder 6)
  - Philippine Islands
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Independence (Folder 8)
  - Pettengill bill (Folder 9)
  - Poetry (Folder 10)
  - Poland (Box 277., Folder 1)
  - Politics, general (Folder 2)
  - Polls (Folder 3)
  - Presidential candidates in 1940
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Dewey, Thomas (Folder 5)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Folder 6)
    - Landon, Alfred (Folder 7)
    - McNutt, Paul (Folder 8)
    - Willkie, Wendell (Folder 9)
  - Presidents, Former (Folder 10)
  - Press releases (Folder 11)
  - Preus, J. A. O. (Folder 12)
  - Private Soldiers and Sailors Legion of the United States of America (Folder 13)
  - Profit system (Folder 14)
  - Progressive Benefit Association (Folder 15)
  - Progressive Party
    - General (Folder 16)
    - Independent Progressive Voters of Minnesota (Folder 17)
  - Progressive Republican Club resolution passed 1921 December 29 (Folder 18)
  - Public ownership (Folder 19)
  - Public Ownership League of America (Box 278., Folder 1)
  - Public works (Folder 2)
  - Public Works Administration (Folder 3)
  - Public Works and Relief Standards Act (Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico (Folder 5)
  - Railroads
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Wages (Folder 7)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation (Folder 8)
  - Red Cross, American National (Folder 9)
  - Refugees (Folder 10)
  - Relief (aid)
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Appropriations (Folder 12)
  - Relief bill
    - To 1936 (Folder 13)
    - 1936-1940 (Folder 14)
  - Relief (charities) (Folder 15)
  - Relief, Minnesota (Folder 16)
  - Relief sent abroad (Folder 17)
  - Republican Party
    - General (Box 279., Folder 1)
    - Minnesota (Folder 2)
    - Platform, 1939-1940 (Folder 3)
    - The Republican, 1921-1923 (Folder 4)
  - Resources (Folder 5)
  - Right to work (Folder 6)
  - Rivers (Folder 7)
  - Romania (Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
    - General (Folder 10-11)
    - General (Box 280., Folder 1)
    - Ambassadors and ministers (Folder 2)
    - Appeals to A. Hitler, 1939 April-November (Folder 3)
    - Cabinet members (Folder 4)
    - Foreign policy (Folder 5)
    - Garner, John Nance (Folder 6)
    - National defense (Folder 7)
    - "Purge," 1938 (Folder 8)
    - Speeches and writings
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Jackson Day speech, 1940 January (Folder 10)
    - Third term (Folder 11)
    - Vatican relations (Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (Folder 13)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti (Box 281., Folder 1)
  - Schall, Thomas D. (Folder 2)
  - Schilplin, Fred (Folder 3)
  - Scrap iron (Folder 4)
  - Sharecroppers (Folder 5)
  - Sheppard-Hill bill (Folder 6)
  - Shipstead, Henrik
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Speeches (Folder 8)
  - Silver (Folder 9)
  - Sinclair, Upton (Folder 10)
  - Sletterdahl, P. J. (Folder 11)
  - Social Democratic Federation, United States of America (Folder 12)
  - Social insurance (Folder 13)
  - Social security (Folder 14)
  - Socialist Party
    - Berger, Victor L. (Box 282., Folder 1)
    - New Leader (Folder 2)
    - Socialist Party of America (Folder 3)
  - Songs for gatherings (Folder 4)
  - The South's problems (Folder 5)
  - Soviet Union
    - General (Folder 6-7)
    - General (Box 283., Folder 1-3)
    - "After Siberia and the Pyrenees Shall It Be the Carpathians?" by Joseph C. Canady (Folder 4)
    - American investment and technological assistance (Folder 5)
    - American Rank and File Trade Union Delegation to Russia, 1927-1928 (Folder 6)
    - American Rank and File Trade Union Delegation to Russia, 1927-1928 (Box 284., Folder 1-3)
    - American Society for Cultural Relations with Russia (Folder 4)
    - Amtorg Trading Corporation (Folder 5)
    - Archangel (Folder 6)
    - Army (Folder 7)
    - Communism (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Folder 9)
    - Description and travel (Box 285., Folder 1)
    - Economy (Folder 2)
    - Farm policy (Folder 3)
    - Foreign relations (Folder 4)
    - Frear, James A. (Folder 5)
    - Friends of the Soviet Union (Folder 6)
    - Jewish freedom (Folder 7)
    - Lenin, Vladimir (Folder 8)
    - Lundeen statements (Folder 9)
    - Recognition by U.S. (Folder 10)
    - Red baiting (Folder 11)
    - Religion (Folder 12)
    - Russian-Scandinavian war, 1939-1940 (Folder 13)
    - Soviet-German pact, 1939 (Box 286., Folder 1)
    - Stalin, Joseph (Folder 2)
    - Swedish colony at Gammalsvenskby (Folder 3)
    - Trade (Folder 4)
    - Trade Union Bulletin, 1927-1929 (Folder 5)
    - Trotsky, Leon (Folder 6)
    - U.S. embassy (Folder 7)
    - Winston, F. S. Transcript of 1926 August 6 interview (Folder 8)
    - War debt owed to U.S. (Folder 9)
    - Wars since 1776 (Folder 10)
  - Spain (Folder 11)
  - Steuben Society of America (Folder 12)
  - Sullivan, George (Folder 13)
  - Swedish organizations; celebrations (Folder 14)
  - Swedish play, Dania Hall, 1922 February 26 (Box 287., Folder 1)
  - Tariff (Folder 2)
  - Taxes (Folder 3)
  - Teachers, American Federation of (Folder 4)
  - Technology/Radio (Folder 5)
  - Teigan, Henry G. (Folder 6)
  - Television (Folder 7)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Folder 8)
  - Third party (Folder 9)
  - Thompson, H. R.
    - Flag Day speech, 1930 June 14 (Folder 10)
    - Memorial Day speech, 1930 May 30 (Folder 11)
  - Townley, A. C. (Folder 12)
  - Townsend Plan (Folder 13)
  - Trade (Folder 14)
  - Trade Union Unity League (Folder 15)
  - Transportation (Folder 16)
  - Travel, Alaska and Hawaii, 1937 (Folder 17)
  - Treaties, secret (Box 288., Folder 1)
  - Trucking (Folder 2)
  - Turkey (Folder 3)
  - Ukraine (Folder 4)
  - Uncle Sam
    - General (Folder 5)
    - 1920
      - July (Folder 6)
      - August (Folder 7)
      - September (Folder 8)
      - October (Folder 9)
      - November (Folder 10)
    - 1922
      - March (Folder 11)
      - November (Folder 12)
  - Unemployment
    - General
      - General (Folder 13)
      - To 1936 (Folder 14)
      - 1936-1940 (Box 289., Folder 1)
    - Bibliography (Folder 2)
    - Compensation laws (Folder 3)
    - Family tragedies (Folder 4)
    - Insurance to 1936 (Folder 5)
    - Reynolds speech (Folder 6)
  - United Conference for Progressive Political Action, 1933 (Folder 7)
  - United Spanish War Veterans. See Veterans - Spanish American War
  - United States. Congress. Senate Committee on Territories and Insular Affairs (Folder 8)
  - United States Employment Service (Folder 9)
  - United States Post Office (Folder 10)
  - United States Supreme Court
    - Clippings, various dates (Folder 11-12)
    - 1936-1940 (Box 290., Folder 1)
  - Versailles Treaty (Folder 2)
  - Veterans
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Civil War (Folder 4)
    - Minnesota (Folder 5)
    - Pensions (Folder 6)
    - Spanish American War (Folder 7)
    - United War Veterans, 1919 (Folder 8)
    - Veterans Political Club of Minnesota, 1930-1931 (Folder 9)
  - Viereck, George S.
    - General (Folder 10)
    - American Monthly (Folder 11)
    - Clippings
      - 1938-1941 (Folder 12)
      - 1942 (Folder 13)
      - Lawsuits (Folder 14)
    - Speeches and writings (Box 291., Folder 1)
    - United States Court of Appeals, Appellant's briefs (Folder 2)
  - Walking (for health) (Folder 3)
  - Wallace's Farmer editorials (Folder 4)
  - War
    - General
      - To 1936 (Folder 5-7)
      - To 1936 (Box 292., Folder 1)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 2-4)
      - 1936-1940 (Box 293., Folder 1-4)
    - Air warfare
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Williams, Alfred J. (Folder 6)
    - Appeal to Reason, Girard, Kansas. "War Lie No. 1" through "War Lie No. 10," various issues, 1921 (Folder 7)
    - Appropriations (Box 294., Folder 1)
    - Armaments (Folder 2)
    - Armistice (Folder 3)
    - Cost of
      - To 1936 (Folder 4)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 5)
    - Economic aspects (Folder 6)
    - Excess profits tax (Folder 7)
    - Germany
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Diplomatic relations severed (Folder 9)
    - Labor (Folder 10)
    - Lundeen's position (Folder 11)
    - Maritime
      - To 1936 (Folder 12)
      - 1936-1940 (Box 295., Folder 1)
    - Materials (Folder 2)
    - Mines (military) (Folder 3)
    - Mobilization
      - To 1936 (Folder 4)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 5)
    - National defense (Folder 6)
    - Neutrality
      - To 1936 (Folder 7)
      - 1936-1940 (Box 296., Folder 1-2)
    - Peace movements (Folder 3-4)
    - Pictures (Folder 5)
    - Poetry and literature (Box 297., Folder 1)
    - Preparedness
      - To 1936 (Folder 2)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 3)
    - Propaganda (Folder 4)
    - Referendum (Folder 5)
    - Reparations (Folder 6)
    - Taxes (Folder 7)
    - War Labor Board, Minneapolis Steel Machinery claims (Folder 8)
    - War Resources Board (Folder 9)
    - Waters, Agnes, white papers (Folder 10)
    - "Why We Went to War," by Newton D. Baker, The American Legion Monthly, April 1927 (Folder 11)
    - World War, 1914-1918
      - Congressional Record, 1917 March 4, December 3 (Box 298., Folder 1)
      - Congressional votes against (Folder 2)
      - Declaration (Folder 3)
      - Lundeen's constituents poll (Folder 4)
      - The War Congress, 1917 (Folder 5)
      - Why we are at war (articles) (Folder 6)
  - Washington, D.C. (Folder 7)
  - Washington, George (Folder 8)
  - Watson, Thomas, 1922-1923 (Folder 9)
  - Webster, Daniel, on the draft (Folder 10)
  - Wendel, Paul H. (Folder 11)
  - West Publishing Company (Folder 12)
  - Willey, Malcolm M. (Box 299., Folder 1)
  - Willkie, Wendell L. (Folder 2)
  - Wilson Package Library (Folder 3)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Folder 4-7)
  - Women's Suffrage Movement
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Anthony, Susan B. (Folder 9)
  - Workers Alliance of America (Folder 10)
  - Workers Party of the United States (Folder 11)
  - Works, John D. (Folder 12)
  - Works Progress Administration
    - 1937 (Box 300., Folder 1)
    - 1938-1940 (Folder 2)
    - Central Labor Union documents (Folder 3)
    - Federal Art Project (Folder 4)
    - Glotzbach, Linus G.
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Appointment hearings
        - General (Folder 6)
        - Against confirmation (Folder 7)
        - For confirmation (Folder 8)
    - Notes supporting H.J. Res. 544 (Folder 9)
    - Strike, 1939 July, August (Folder 10)
    - Strike, 1939 July, August (Box 301., Folder 1)
    - Telegrams (Folder 2)
    - Trials of strikers
      - 1939-1940 (Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Folder 4)
      - Defense funds (Folder 5)
      - Governor Stassen's position (Folder 6)
      - Right to strike (Folder 7)
    - Unemployment and poverty (Folder 8)
    - Woodrum bill
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Amendments (Folder 10)
    - World federation (Folder 11)
    - World court (Folder 12)
  - Wright, Orville (Box 302., Folder 1)
  - Yankee Clipper flight from Washington, D.C. to London, England, 1939 June (Folder 2-3)
  - Youngquist amendment to eliminate state property tax levy (Folder 4)
  - Youth (Folder 5)
  - Youth Congress (Folder 6)
  - Yugoslavia (Folder 7)
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1894-1944.
  See also CORRESPONDENCE, Boxes 8, 33, 58, 166-186, 209
  - General (Box 303., Folder 1)
  - Address books (Folder 2-3)
  - Automobiles (Folder 4)
  - Bar Associations (Folder 5)
  - Biography (Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn School, Beresford, South Dakota (Folder 7)
  - Carleton College. See also CORRESPONDENCE, 1906-1932, Box 5 (Folder 8)
  - Carleton College
    - General (Box 304., Folder 1-2)
    - Athenian Literary Society (Folder 3)
  - Christmas cards
    - Lists (Folder 4)
    - Received in 1933 (Folder 5)
    - Received in 1937 (Folder 6)
    - Received in 1938, 1939 (Box 305., Folder 1)
  - Church affiliation
    - Confirmation (Folder 2)
    - Augustana Lutheran Church (Folder 3)
    - Wesley Methodist Church (Folder 4)
  - Contributions (Folder 5)
  - Dayton, Iowa, High School
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Class of 1895's twentieth reunion (Folder 7)
  - Death of Ernest Lundeen
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Bills paid and outstanding (Folder 9)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board report of (airplane) accident of August 31, 1940 (Folder 10)
    - Clippings (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - Letters of condolence (Folder 12)
      - Office business (Folder 13)
    - Estate (Box 306., Folder 1)
    - Grave headstone (Folder 2)
    - Investigation of the airplane crash (Folder 3)
    - Memorial services (Folder 4)
    - Office files storage (Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Central Airlines (Folder 6)
    - Posthumous lawsuits
      - Pearson, Drew and Robert Allen (Folder 7)
      - Viereck, George S. (Folder 8)
      - Winchell, Walter (Folder 9)
    - Radio broadcast by Mrs. Lundeen to refute Walter Winchell broadcast that questioned Lundeen's patriotism
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Drafts of statements (Folder 11)
      - Reactions (Folder 12)
      - Reactions (Box 307., Folder 1-2)
      - Successor appointed (Folder 3)
  - Divorce from Ethel L. Whipple Lundeen (Folder 4)
  - Finances
    - 1938 (Folder 5)
    - Bills and receipts (Folder 6)
    - Budget (Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1940 (Box 308., Folder 1)
    - Cash account
      - 1896 (Folder 2)
      - 1903 (Folder 3)
      - 1937-1940 (Folder 4)
    - Franklin Liquidating Trust (Folder 5)
    - Income from law firm (Folder 6)
    - Investments (Folder 7)
    - Personal (Folder 8)
    - Postal savings (Folder 9)
    - Taxes
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Income
        - General (Folder 11)
        - 1932 (Folder 12)
        - 1933 (Folder 13)
        - 1934 (Folder 14)
        - 1935 (Folder 15)
        - 1936 (Folder 16)
        - 1937 (Folder 17)
        - 1938 (Folder 18)
        - 1939 (Folder 19)
        - 1940 (Folder 20)
    - W. B. Moses & Sons (Folder 21)
  - Health examinations (Folder 22)
  - Insurance policies
    - General (Box 309., Folder 1)
    - Automobile (Folder 2)
    - Continental Casualty Company (Folder 3)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society (Folder 4)
    - Northwestern Mutual Life (Folder 5)
  - Inventory of jewelry (Folder 6)
  - Lawsuits (all are versus Lundeen). See also CAMPAIGN FILE, Box 324
    - 1928 (Folder 7)
    - Charles A. Anderson Company and the Minnesota Loan and Trust Company (Folder 8)
    - Erickson & Ledstrom, Inc. (Folder 9)
    - Golling & Hesse (Folder 10)
    - W. H. Hiatt (Folder 11)
    - J. W. Hulme Company (Folder 12)
    - Kremer Motor Company (Folder 13)
    - Betsy Madison-Munson (Folder 14)
    - Clara H. Martin (Folder 15)
    - F. W. Nothaft (Folder 16)
    - Security Mutual Life Insurance Company (Folder 17)
    - Ida Sjoberg (Folder 18)
    - Amos Wells (Folder 19)
  - Legislature, Minnesota
    - General (Box 310., Folder 1)
    - Clippings (Folder 2)
  - Lundeen family
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Aurora, 1912 (Folder 4)
    - Genealogy (Folder 5)
    - Lundin, Charles Henry (Folder 6)
    - Memorial monument (Folder 7)
    - Lundeen, Norma Ward
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Campaign 1942
        - General (Box 311., Folder 1)
        - Speeches and statements (Folder 2)
      - Clippings (Folder 3)
      - Correspondence
        - Undated-1933 (Folder 4)
        - 1934-1940 (Folder 5)
        - 1941-1942 (Folder 6)
        - 1943-1944 (Folder 7)
        - To answer (Box 312., Folder 1)
        - Doolittle, Dudley (Folder 2)